livejasmin.at 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy | LiveJasmin

Welcome to our Privacy Policy!

livejasmin is an adult entertainment site, which offers live cam performances and other related adult services.

When you use these services, you will share some personal information with us. Because we want you to enjoy our services in a peaceful and trustworthy way, please be assured that we are fully dedicated to the protection of your personal information.

Because your privacy is so important to us, we provide you with this Privacy Policy, explaining how we collect, use and share your personal information, so that you can make informed choices about the use of your data.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. We have tried to write it in a way, which is free of long boring sentences and legal terms. You can contact us if you have any question about our privacy practices or about what we are doing with your personal information. We will be happy to provide you any assistance you may need.

## Who Decides "How" and "Why" Your Personal Data is Processed?

The company, which decides how and why your personal data is processed, and which is called "Data Controller" is:

Duodecad IT Services Luxembourg S.à r.l., a private limited liability company incorporated in Luxembourg, with registered address at 44, Avenue John F. Kennedy, L-1855, Luxembourg, Grand Duchy of Luxembourg, registered with the Luxembourg Trade and Companies Register under number 171.358.

## What Personal Data do We Process?

We collect, use, share, transfer, and store different types of your personal data as a result of your visit of and/or use of our services on our site.

The personal data we collect includes the following categories of data:

  1. Personal data you give to us

    * When you create a customer account on our site

When you create an account on our site, we require important details about you:

      * an email address

      * a username

      * a password

To give yourself more visibility and presence on our site, and attract more Models, especially our high demanded Models, you can complete "My Profile" in your account settings. By doing so, you are free to provide some additional information about you, such as:

      * a nickname

      * your gender

      * your age

      * your location

      * your sexual preferences

      * your interests and hobbies

      * your personality traits/character

      * what do you do for a living

      * what do you do for fun

      * what makes you feel special

Providing this information about you in your profile is optional. With your consent only, all Models will be able to see this data. You can delete this data from your profile at any moment, which will not affect your use of the site. You can also set your privacy level in your profile if you want to share these data only with the Models who you have private chatted with or if you want to keep your profile private.

    * When you contact our Billing & Customer Support

We collect all information you choose to share with our Billing & Customer Support, like:

      * your personal e-mail

      * the services, the Model or customer username associated with your request

      * your comments or opinions about a Model

      * your conversations with the Support Team

More generally, when you communicate with us in any other way, we will collect whatever information you provide us with.

    * When you purchase credits

When you purchase credits to participate on our site, depending on the payment method you choose, we may collect and process your identification information (first name, last name, country, ZIP code) and payment information.

    * When you refer-a-friend

When you refer a friend to our site(subject to our Terms and Conditions, and, as the case may be, the terms described in the dashboard related to the referral program in the user menu of your account), we do not collect any of his/her personal data before he/she becomes a Member on our site. More precisely, when your friend clicks on the referral link you shared with him/her, we generate a referral number and keep only this data. This standalone information is not qualified as identifiable information. It may only be linked with other data of the referred friend when the latter decides to join the site, which will only then lead to his/her identification.

  2. Personal Information we get when you use our services

We collect certain information about you when you are using our services and navigate on our site.

Concretely, this means that, when you visit our site or use our services, even if you have not created an account or logged in, we collect certain information about you.

    * Usage information

We collect information about your activity on our site and about how you interact with the features of our site. Basically, we know:

      * your activity history on our site and the special features you used on the site, for example, if you voted in awards, sent a feedback after private chat, rated and/or put a Model in your list of favorites, made a Video/Voice Call to the Model, subscribed to Model’s MyStory, etc.

      * the time you spend in private chat, who are the Models and categories of Models (for example, Asian girls, Latin women, black hair) you watched;

We also collect information about your communications with the Models, such as:

      * the username of the Model

      * the time and date of your communications

      * the type of communications (for example, a wall message, private chat, etc...)

Moreover, if you participate in our loyalty program, referred as Elite Program in our Terms and Conditions, we know what your mask ranking is (i.e., the information you also see in your profile when you are connected to the site). In this respect, please note that we never keep the history of your mask ranking.

If you share content with Models (for example, pictures), such content will be stored on our system for the proper technical execution of the service.

    * Content information

For a technical purpose, we store on our system content you create and/or post and/or transmit on/via our site (for example pictures) and information about the content you create or provide.

We also collect, any information you communicate to and/or share with Models on the site, such as the messages you send in private chat or during live shows.

If you turn on your microphone in private chat, we may retain your audio feed for a limited period of 6 months to protect our rights or defend ourselves against any claims. Any such data retained shall be held in our secured records with restricted access. Please note that in case you turn on your camera in private chat, we never record or keep in any way your camera feed. We also do not allow our Models to record or capture your camera or audio feeds during private shows. Such action is prohibited on our site.

If you use the Video/Voice Call feature on our site (to call the Model when she is offline), we do not record or process your communication data with the Model. Your communication is private.

We collect any other communication data such as telephone conversations, chat logs, text messages, faxes and letters you send to us.

    * Log data and device information

We automatically collect log data and information from or about your computer, phone, or other devices you use to access our services or navigate on our site. This includes:

      * your IP address

      * the date and time you logged into your account

      * pages viewed

      * types of features you use

      * the hardware, software or internet browser you use

      * information about your computer’s operating system, like application version

      * your language settings

      * identifiers associated with cookies or other technologies that may uniquely identify your device or browser

If you are using a mobile device, we might also collect:

      * data that identifies your mobile device

      * device-specific settings and characteristics

      * location details

      * app crashes and other system activity

    * Information collected by cookies and other technologies

Like many websites and applications, we use cookies and other technologies (such as web beacons, web storage, and unique advertising identifiers) to collect information about your activity, browser, and device.

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually remove or reject browser cookies through the settings on your browser or device. Keep in mind, though, that blocking cookies may negatively affect your use of the services on our site.

We are also using [Hotjar](https://www.hotjar.com/) services to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users’ experience (e.g., how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular device's IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking on [this link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy).

You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of your livejasmin site usage data and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies by following this [opt-out link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out).

To learn more about how we use cookies and your choices, please check out our [Cookies Policy]().

  3. Personal data we receive from third parties

    * We collect information that the Models provide about you in the course of the chat conversation or communication with our Billing and Support Team. 

    * We are also dealing with partner ad networks, which help us to promote our site. For example, we might receive information about your experiences and interactions from our partner ad networks.

    * We are also managing an ad network and promotional tools ourselves and may receive information about your experiences and interactions with our ads and promotional tools published/used on third party or affiliated sites.

    * If a friend, Member of our site, invited you to join us, through a referral link he/she shared with you beforehand, please note that your friend did not provide us with your personal information. He/she only shared the link with you on his/her behalf to be able to receive a reward. The information we process when you decide to click on the referral link is a random referral number that we store in our system/databases for a limited period. We use this information exclusively to determine if the Member who invited you to join our site and yourself, are both eligible to receive a referral fee reward/credit. The referral number, as standalone information, contains no identifiable information about you. It is, thus, considered as a piece of anonymous information. It may only be linked with identifiable information about you when you decide to register on our site.

  4. Personal data we collect from publicly available sources

We collect publicly available information about you only when it is necessary to prevent fraud and illegal activities on our site (for example, when we suspect that you are using a false or stolen credit card, when we witness child abuse cases, or pedophile activity, etc.).

This data may comprise publicly available information you share on social media like Facebook, your blog and/or site, and any other public data available on the internet.

This information is always associated or combined with the data we collect through our site to finalize our investigation before reporting any fraud and illegal activities to authorities. We never use publicly available data for any other purpose.

  5. Special category of data

    * livejasmin is an adult entertainment site, and due to its nature and purpose, we may process data about you which could reflect your sexual interests or preferences.

There are three situations where we are susceptible to process your sensitive data:

    * If you consent to the use of the "livejasmin cookie" as detailed in clause 3.7 "Personalized Content" to personalize the content of our site for you.

Please be aware that you can change your opinion regarding the processing of your sensitive data in your consent settings at any time by opting out from Personalized Content. If you do so, we will no longer personalize the content of the site for you. You may, therefore, face some negative user experience.

    * When you use our site and purchase services. More precisely, when you interact with the Models or purchase services (like when you watch live cam shows, take a Model in a private chat, buy her surprises, or any other service you purchase) we process and store information related to your activity (e.g., the category of Models you purchased services from or the Models whose special services you subscribed for, etc.) in order to provide you with the services you requested for and to enhance your experience on the site.

Due to the explicit meaning of each category name, as well as the types of Models you request services from (e.g., Asian girls, White Ladies, Latin Women, etc.), it is possible, although not certain, that the chosen categories indicate your online sexual preferences.

Please be aware that you can change your opinion regarding the processing of your sensitive data in your consent settings at any time. However, please note that refusing to provide or revoking your consent to have this data collected and used means that you will not be able to log into your account and use the services, as we will not be able to provide you with the services without processing such information.

    * When after creating an account, you are freely providing us with details about your sexual interests. More precisely, you can indicate certain sexual preferences in your account settings, which is optional. You can choose to provide such information to give yourself more visibility and presence on our site. In case you freely indicated your sexual preferences in your account settings and want to delete this data, you can easily remove it from your account profile. This will not affect your use of the site.

We understand that the information we have about you may not explicitly reflect the reality of your life outside of the site. Your online preferences may only be a role that you choose to play in a virtual environment. However, to provide you with the utmost level of data protection, we categorize such type of data under the sensitive data category, which is highly protected and handled with the utmost care.

Because your online sexual preferences and other data relating to your sexual interests are essential aspects of privacy, we are maintaining very high technology security standards. We are periodically proceeding with controls and assessments of our security measures, to guarantee a trustworthy environment.

## Why do We Process Your Personal Data?

We use the information we collect for the following purposes:

  1. Open your Member account and provide you with the services

    1. Primarily, we use the personal data you give us when you create your online account to open and administer this account, to allow you to do many activities on our site, and to use features that are of your interest. Your account allows you also to purchase credits and benefit from paying and non-paying services.

Your account is also a way to exercise control over your personal data. Through your account, you can manage your purchases, benefit from special offers, and manage your profile and account settings.

We process this information to perform the contract that we have with you and provide you with the services you requested. If you fail to provide minimum details about you, the consequence will be that we will not be able to create an account and allow you to use our services.

    2. Secondly, we allow you to provide additional information in your account if you are willing to share these data with our Models to attract them, especially our high demanded Models. You are in control of what information you use to complete your profile.

We process this information given your consent. We have provided you with an informative notice placed on the page of your profile settings so that you are aware of the use of these data and how we are sharing them. You can always revoke this consent by erasing these data directly from your account in your profile settings page. Be assured that the erasure of these data is instantaneous. We have no copies of any such data; neither do we have any necessity to keep these data for any reason whatsoever. You are the one who chooses the information you wish to share with our Models.

  2. Improve and promote our services

    * We use a limited portion of your data for analytical and statistical purposes. We place great emphasis on the improvement of our services and the enhancement of your experience as a Member or Guest.

To better understand your needs and how we can improve our services, we compile the information you gave to us or that we collected about you when visiting pages on our site or while using our services, to detect general trends regarding the preferences/habits of our users. This helps us, for example, to generate statistics reports on our customers’ activity based on the categories of Models viewed, the countries, or the purchases.

    * We also use your personal data for testing purposes, troubleshooting and improving the functionality and quality of our online entertainment services. Our main goal is to optimize our site and services to your needs, which makes them easier and more enjoyable to use.

    * We share very limited characteristics about you with the Models registered on our site, so that they can deliver a service adapted to you. Please see point 5 "WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR DATA?" to learn more.

    * We use limited information to tailor our services for you. For example, when you visit and log in on our site we use your IP address to determine the country where you are from, and display our webpages in your language (within the limits of the languages available on the site), so if you visit or login on our site from the United States, our site will automatically display content in English.

    * We have affiliate programs through which webmasters or other third parties can help us to promote our sites, for example by creating a reproduction of our well-known sites. Those sites can include only certain categories of Models.

We share some limited information about you with the webmasters or other third parties participating in our programs, to help them to set up, maintain and optimize their marketing campaigns or promotional activities. This also allows them to track their income. Please see point 5 "WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR DATA?" to learn more.

    * Finally, please be aware that any information that you made public on our site, such as comments on the public wall of Models, may appear on search engines results, together with your username.

We process this information given our legitimate interest in developing and improving our site and our users’ experience, as well as to promote our services and our sites. When we use cookies or similar technologies for the same purpose (i.e., product enhancement and improvement), we rely on your consent to the use of cookies, including third parties cookies. To learn more about how we use cookies and your choices, please check out our [Cookies Policy](). 

  3. Customer relationship management and communication with you

    * We provide Customer and Billing Support service 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. Sharing your personal details with our Customer and Billing Support Team allows us to respond to any question you might have about our services.

All your communications with our Customer and Billing Support and all information you provide in the course of such communications, including any review or opinion about the services of a Model, are stored and reviewed so that we may respond to your request. We can also ensure this way full compliance of all users of our site with our terms and conditions.

Some of the recorded communications with you are used for training purposes of our employees within the Customer and Billing Support so that we can ensure customer service excellence. 

Finally, be aware that, when receiving a request or claim of a customer, our Customer and Billing Support Team can access all information you give to us and all usage information we collected about you. We want to make sure that our Customer and Billing Support has all the information needed to respond appropriately and immediately to your request.

Please note that the Customer and Billing Support may also communicate with you through emails or any other means, if appropriate.

    * Please note that we may also communicate with you through emails or any other means, if appropriate, to inform you of certain changes regarding our site or certain events, for example, when you successfully register on our site.

The use of your personal information is necessary to perform the contract that you have with us, notably to deliver appropriate customer services to you.

  4. Payment

    * Depending on the payment method you choose, we use your identification data and payment information to process transactions.

The use of your personal information is necessary to perform the contract that you have with us. If you purchase credits, we will use your information to execute the payment and provide you with the services.

  5. Ensure a safe and trustworthy environment

    * Because we want to create and ensure a safe environment where you can peacefully enjoy our services, we use your personal data to detect and prevent fraud and other illegal activities on our site.

    * We also use your data to detect potential breaches to the rules of our site. The rules of the site are explained in our terms and conditions.

    * Finally, we use your personal information for security purposes and risk assessment, such as to authenticate you on our site and verify your identity.

We process this information given our legitimate interest in ensuring compliance with the rules of our site, fraud detection and prevention, as well as, information, system, network and cyber security.

  6. Sending of messages and marketing emails

When you use one of our services, to stay in touch with us, we will send you informative messages and direct marketing to keep you up to date with the release of new features and/or services on our site, special promotions/offers and more.

For marketing purposes, we will use the information you gave to us and the information we get about you when navigating on our site and using our services.

Based on this information, we will send you marketing emails tailored to your tastes or to certain of your characteristics (such as your country, the time you spend on the site, the amount of credit purchased). Be assured that we will never use your sensitive data for marketing purposes.

If you participate in the referral program and refer people to our site, please note that you are the one and not us, who is sending emails and sharing the referral link with your friends. We will use the information we collect through the referral link, once activated by your friend only, to administer such a referral program and to evaluate both of your eligibility for a reward. In the event a referral program is deactivated for whatever reason subject to our Terms and Conditions, any data retained to administer such program will be immediately erased from our system.

To evaluate the results and success of our marketing initiatives, we may pseudonymize your email address and use it to generate statistical results. Such statistics are in the form of aggregated data and not personal information (for example, the number of users per country who are receiving marketing communications).

We may also use your email to send you an invitation to participate in surveys so we can learn more about your experience and satisfaction with us or to improve our service.

The sending of messages and marketing emails is based on our legitimate interest. You can easily unsubscribe at any time through the related link in our emails. You can also very easily opt-out from direct marketing at any time in your "Consent Settings". Opting-out means that you might miss out information on new services and special offers.

  7. Personalized Content 

We are using software which is following your behavior on our site (e.g., when you are navigating on our site, viewing live streams, looking at Models’ profiles, visiting the pages/walls of the Models, watching live cam feeds, etc.). This software is enabling our site to display for you the Models who could be of your interest.

To provide you with personalized content we process and store information related to your activity (e.g., the category of Models you watched or the page you visited).

You can agree to the use of this software through the “personalized content banner” appearing on the right bottom corner on the site. Thus, you can agree that we follow your preferences when browsing our site that might reflect your sexual interests to personalize the content specifically for you, providing you the best experience.

Your acceptance of using this software means that a cookie (i.e., the "personalized content" cookie or the so-called "livejasmin" cookie) is placed in your browser, which helps the site to adapt to your needs. Hence, you will quickly find content displayed on the site based on your preferences. More precisely, on your next visit, a webpage based on your preferences from the previous activity will be displayed.

We rely on your consent to create a customized experience for you.

If you are a Guest who consented to the content personalization, and you decide to withdraw said consent, go simply to your browser settings and delete the "livejasmin" cookie. If you face any difficulties to opt-out from content personalization, feel free to contact the Customer Support at [help@livejasmin.com](mailto:help@livejasmin.com).

If you are a Member who consented to the content personalization and you decide to withdraw said consent, you can opt-out in your Privacy Settings through your account.

Please note that revoking your consent to content personalization may negatively affect your experience on our website.

  8. Loyalty program participation

To show more loyalty to you and to allow you to earn points and achieve ranks, we operate a loyalty program. We consider this program as a game and entertainment/amusement initiative.

The participation in the loyalty program is based on the contract we have with you. Of course, the entertainment you receive through the participation in the loyalty program is a secondary service to the main service you are provided with on our site. Therefore, if you do not want to be part of it, you can contact our Customer Support and request the cancellation of your participation. This will not affect your use of the site.

  9. Comply with any legal requirements and enforce our legal rights

We may rely on a legal obligation to process your personal data. For example, we retain your transaction information to maintain legally required accounting records.

We may also use your information to respond to requests of competent authorities or given our legitimate interest to establish, exercise or defend legal claims. We also use your data, if necessary, to investigate issues with the bank processing your payment or with a debt collector, in case of unpaid transactions, chargebacks or refunds.

We may combine your information with information lawfully obtained from other third-party sources and use it for the above purposes.

## How do We Protect And How Long Do We Retain Your Personal Data?

We implement serious security measures, including technical and organizational security measures, to grant maximum protection to your personal information against unauthorized access, modification, disclosure or deletion. Your data is protected by our highly sophisticated security systems.

We actively implement data loss prevention systems against leakage, theft and data breach to ensure that our site and the entire IT infrastructure related to it are updated against the latest network security vulnerabilities. We periodically test our IT systems and do sophisticated penetration tests. Our site incorporates the most advanced security technologies available to ensure maximum safety of its users and the safekeeping of their related information.

We will retain your personal data for as long as we consider it necessary to:

  * Enable you to use our services and provide our services to you, including maintaining your customer account;

  * Comply with our legal obligations. For example, we may keep some of your information for tax, legal reporting and auditing obligations. Please note that, according to Luxembourg legislation, financial information shall be kept for a period of ten (10) years.

  * Conduct our business and for our legitimate business interests, such as establishing, exercising or defending legal claims, chargeback prevention, fraud detection and prevention, hindering any other illegal activity on our site, and enhancing safety. For example, if we close or suspend your account for fraud or illegal activities, we may retain certain information about you to prevent you from opening a new account in the future. Such information shall also be kept available in case of ongoing judicial proceedings/and or investigations. As part of our fraud detection and prevention process, we also blacklist all former usernames for a certain time. Therefore, a former username cannot be used for a new registration. For chargeback prevention, we retain your chat logs and your log data, device and usage information for a maximum period of 120 days from your last purchase on the site.

  * Protect our site and your personal information from accidental or malicious loss and destruction. Residual copies of your personal information may not be removed from our backup systems for a very limited time (usually 30 days).

Some copies of your information (e.g., log records) may also remain in our database, but are disassociated from personal identifiers.

In case you have a question about a specific retention period for certain categories of personal data we process about you, please contact us via the contact details provided in point 9 "HOW TO CONTACT US?"

## With Whom do We Share Your Data?

We share a portion of your personal data with the following parties:

  1. With the Models

Your contract with us secures your ability to benefit from and purchase services relating to adult entertainment from Models.

    * Regarding your profile information, by default, the only data element visible to the Model is your username.

However, you may choose to share with a Model other information about you that you added to "My Profile" in your account settings, like your gender, age, location, interests, etc.; you may also connect your camera in private chat in order to visually communicate with the Model or just turn on your microphone. The Model is not allowed to record the video and voice data you provide.

In any case, please keep in mind that you can manage the visibility of the information you added in "My Profile" by selecting the appropriate option in your privacy settings and therefore decide who can see the information you put on your profile.

In case you decide to share additional content with the Models, such as pictures, please note that you are fully responsible of such sharing of information and that we cannot be held responsible of any disclosure you freely made.

    * What else do we show about you to the Models?

      * As the Models are appearing on several sites at the same time (all our sites and affiliated sites), we show them from which site you are visiting from

      * We show them a special icon, if you subscribed to their fan club

      * We show them a special icon, if you added them in your favorites

      * We show them a special icon, if you are a regular Member on a site and already purchased a certain number of credits, so that they know that you deserve extra attention and a good service. Please be aware that you can deactivate this feature, by contacting us to the email address or address indicated in point 9 "HOW TO CONTACT US?"

      * We show them also your loyalty mask. However, you can set up in your Privacy Settings page your preferences about the sharing of your mask ranking with the Models. You can choose to share your mask ranking only with Models with whom you had private chats, or you can keep it private.

      * Moreover, when you initiate a private chat with a Model, no one can access your video feed (in case you turn your camera on). As regards your voice feed (in case you turn on your microphone only limited staff within our organization can access on a "need to know" basis this data, to ensure what service you requested precisely from the Model, and to handle claims, notably in the event of a chargeback.

      * Finally, we share with the Models some information about you that was collected in the course of your use of the site (i.e., behavior data). For example your willingness (what you usually like the Model to do in a private show, like dancing, striptease show, etc.), or the information about what features you use (Game, Surprise, etc.). This information is shared with the Models exclusively during the private chat for know-your-customer purposes, on our behalf, allowing the Models to know you better and provide you the service tailored to your needs. The Model is not allowed to record this data, but she can take notes, so that the next time you are in private with her, she knows what can make you happy.

  2. With other users of the site and with the public

    * When you chat with a Model in a free chat, other users of our site can see your username and the messages you write. Also, they can see if you become a King of the Room and the number of credits you spent on surprises for said purpose. This information is, however, not personal data, as the other users cannot retrieve and link somehow this data with other information that may lead to your identification. In this respect, we remind you of the terms of our contract under which you are not allowed to choose a username which contains your personal information (such as your real name) or information that may allow another user to connect it to your real identity (such as the public username you use for social platforms, like Facebook, Twitter, etc.). In case you decide to choose a username that can lead to your identification, please note that you are fully responsible for such action and that we cannot be held responsible of any identification another user of our site can make.

    * Also, if you post comments on a Model’s wall, other users will see your comments. Your comments and username may also be visible on the results of a search engine, like Google, for example. Therefore, if you do not want other users or the public in general to see your comments, please do not post comments on a Model’s wall. Therefore, if you do not want other users or the public in general to see your comments, please do not post comments on a Model’s wall.

    * Moreover, if you participate in the loyalty program, other users will see your loyalty mask next to your username when you write a message to a Model in a free chat. Please note that these two data elements (username and mask) when shared with the other users are not personal data, as they cannot lead to your identification. However, you can still set up in your Privacy Settings page (although this is not a privacy issue) your preferences about the sharing of your mask with the other users if it amuses you. Of course, you can keep your mask private.

Be assured that other Guests or Members of livejasmin will not access any information about you from the moment you enter into a private chat.

  3. Entities of our company’s group

We share your personal information with the following companies of our group based in Luxembourg, Hungary, and the US, as they are helping us to deliver the services to you:

    * Jasmin IP S.à r.l., 44, Avenue John F. Kennedy, L-1855, Luxembourg, Grand Duchy of Luxembourg

    * Docler Services S.à r.l., 44, Avenue John F. Kennedy, L-1855, Luxembourg, Grand Duchy of Luxembourg

    * Docler IP S.à r.l., 44, Avenue John F. Kennedy, L-1855, Luxembourg, Grand Duchy of Luxembourg

    * Docler SSC Kft, Expo tér 5-7, H-1101, Budapest, Hungary

    * Jasmin IP S.à r.l. Hungary Branch, Expo tér 5-7, H-1101, Budapest, Hungary

    * Docler Media LLC, 10811 Washington Blvd, Culver City, CA 90232, USA

    * Escalion S.à r.l., 44, Avenue John F. Kennedy, L-1855, Luxembourg, Grand Duchy of Luxembourg

  4. Webmasters participating in our affiliate programs

We have affiliate programs through which webmasters and other third parties can help us to promote our sites, for example, by creating reproduction of our well-known sites. Those sites can include only certain categories of Models.

Please note that, whether you registered directly on one of our sites or on one of our affiliated sites, we stay the controller of your personal data. For example, when you create an account or purchase credits, the personal information that you give for these purposes goes directly to us. The webmaster cannot see or access your personal data. He/she is only a technical operator and business partner helping us to promote our activity. In no event, you are a client/customer of a webmaster.

We only share some limited information with them that however cannot lead to your direct identification. This minimum information helps them to set up, maintain and optimize their marketing campaigns or promotional activities. This also allows them to track their income. This information consists of your registration date, the site where you come from, register or purchase credits, your country, your username, the packages of credits bought (in case the webmaster was eligible for a commission) and certain device information (your operating system, your browser type and the type of device (e.g. tablet, mobile, desktop)).

Please be aware that we will never share with them any information leading to your direct identification, for example, your real name, your address, your email address, your payment details or your IP address.

  5. Service providers

We use carefully selected and trusted third parties, who act as service providers to our site.

We ensure that they are bound by contractually binding obligations to process information we share with them in accordance with our instructions, this Privacy Policy and all applicable data protection laws.

As we constantly work on the development and enhancement of the technology to support our site, our third party service providers we are using may regularly change. Such entities mainly belong to the following areas: (a) business intelligence and analytics; (b) customer care; (c) marketing and sales; (d) fraud prevention.

  6. Payment providers and financial institutions

When you purchase credits, depending on the payment method you choose, your payment may be processed by a third party bank or a payment processor, and you may share with this party certain details, as well as payment information to complete a transaction.

You may receive transactional emails from this party confirming the order, including dispatch, possible refunds, and follow-up invitations to leave feedback for this party.

If you share information with third parties directly, this Privacy Policy does not govern the processing of your personal information by these third parties.

If you choose the payment method "Credit/Debit card", your transaction will be handled by Escalion S.à r.l., which is part of our companies group and located in Luxembourg. For your information, you can find its privacy policy [here](https://www.escalion.com/en/privacy-policy-customer)

When a chargeback is requested by you or by the holder of the credit card used to make the transaction, we have, in certain cases, to share some information about you and your use of the services with the processing bank.

We may furthermore share information with relevant financial institutions, if we consider it strictly necessary for fraud detection and prevention purposes.

  7. Law enforcement agencies or governmental authorities

To the extent permitted by applicable laws, we may also share information with law enforcement agencies or authorities, if such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with our legal obligations, (b) respond to information requests for fraud investigations and alleged illegal activities, (c) enforce and administer our terms and conditions, and/or (d) protect our rights or defend ourselves against any claims.

  8. Business transfers

Finally, please also note that your information may be transferred to another entity of our group following some internal reorganization or to another third party entity in case of sale, reorganization, restructuring, merger and/or acquisition or any other disposal whatsoever at group or company level resulting that part (more than 50%) or whole of our business (or related assets) is either directly or indirectly transferred or falling under control of a third party acquirer, provided the latter and/or the other group company in case of internal reorganisation operates within same or similar line of business as ours and commits to comply with this Privacy Policy.

## How do We Transfer Your Personal Data Outside of the European Economic Area?

As we are a Luxembourg based company, we comply with the EU Data Protection Regulation commonly called "GDPR" (If you want to learn more you can check: [EU Regulation 2016/679 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC](https://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/PDF/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=FR)), which provides a high level of protection of your personal data.

In the course of the operation and exploitation of the site and the provision of the services, your personal information may be transferred outside of the European Economic Area ("EEA") to our affiliated companies or to third parties data processors located in the US and other countries outside of where you live, for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy.

If we transfer your personal data outside of the EEA, we endeavor to ensure that your rights and freedoms in respect of the processing of your personal data are adequately and appropriately protected. For this purpose, we utilize the Standard Contractual Clauses approved by the European Commission that you can find [here](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/model-contracts-transfer-personal-data-third-countries_en).

## What are Your Rights Regarding Your Personal Data?

We did our best to explain what your rights are and how you can exercise them. If, despite of our below explanations, you are still unsure about the actions you can take or the conditions of exercise of your rights, do not worry, our Support Team will provide you with all the assistance you need when exercising your rights.

You may also contact us, at any time, before exercising any of your rights, and we will reply to your request as quickly as possible.

Please note that we created a specific interface called "Privacy Settings" in your account settings for you to be able to exercise certain of your rights easily.

Our Support Team will provide you with information on actions taken within one month of the day of receipt of your request. Only in exceptional circumstances, when we face complex and a high number of requests, we may extend this period of response up to two further months.

Please note that rights may be exercised free of charge. However, unfounded or excessive requests, in particular because of their repetitive character, will lead to the payment of a fee.

Please also understand that, because your privacy is so important for us, our Support Team may need to duly verify your identity and ask you to provide additional information before executing your request.

  1. Data access and data portability

You have the right to access the personal information that we hold about you by requesting a copy of your personal data free of charge through the "Data Download" section in your account settings.

Upon verification of your identity, your request will be sent to our Support Team.

If we consider that your request is manifestly unfounded or excessive (for example, because you requested a copy of your data numerous times in a short period), we may refuse to act or charge a reasonable fee taking into account the administrative costs for providing you the information.

In certain cases, you may also be entitled to request copies of personal information that you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format and/or request us to transmit this information to another service provider (where technically feasible). For this purpose, you can send an email to [privacy@livejasmin.com](mailto:privacy@livejasmin.com).

  2. Rectification of inaccurate or incomplete data

You have the right to request that we correct any inaccuracies in your personal data.

For this purpose, you can send an email to [privacy@livejasmin.com](mailto:privacy@livejasmin.com).

  3. Data retention and erasure

If you no longer want us to use your information, you can request that we erase your personal information and close your account. Request for account cancellation or closure will be considered as a request for erasure of your personal data. In such case, please select "Forget my Data" in the "Privacy Settings" section of your account settings.

Your request will be sent to our Support Team who will contact you to learn more about your request. However, if you face any difficulties, please contact us at any time.

Please note that if you request the erasure of your personal information, we will retain your personal data for as long as we consider it necessary to:

    * Comply with our legal obligations. For example, we may keep some of your information for tax, legal reporting and auditing obligations. Please note that according to Luxembourg legislation, financial related information shall be kept for a period of ten (10) years.

    * Conduct our business and for our legitimate business interests, such as establishing, exercising or defending legal claims, chargeback prevention, fraud detection and prevention, hindering any other illegal activity on our site, and enhancing safety. For example, if we close or suspend your account for fraud or illegal activities, we may retain certain information about you to prevent you from opening a new account in the future. Such information shall also be kept available in case of ongoing judicial proceedings/and or investigations. As part of our fraud detection and prevention process, we also blacklist all former usernames for a certain time. Therefore, a former username cannot be used for new registration.

    * Protect our site and your personal information from accidental or malicious loss and destruction. Residual copies of your personal information may not be removed from our backup systems for a very limited time (usually 30 days).

Some copies of your information (e.g., log records) may also remain in our database, but are disassociated from personal identifiers.

  4. Right to object

    * We process your data for a variety of reasons as explained in "3. WHY DO WE PROCESS YOUR PERSONAL DATA?". Applicable law may entitle you to require us not to process your personal information for certain specific purposes where such processing is based on legitimate interest. If you object to such processing we will stop processing your personal data for these purposes.

In specific situations, we may have to refuse the execution of your request. This would be the case where we have legitimate grounds to continue such processing or if we have to establish, exercise or defend legal claims.

Please keep in mind that objecting to the use of your data might disable the use of your account.

    * Please note that you may, at any time, ask us to stop sending you marketing emails by opting-out in your account settings.

  5. Right to restriction of processing

You have the right to request that we hold your personal data in "limbo", while other challenges are resolved.

Basically, you can ask us to put on hold the use of your data in 4 cases:

    * If you contest the fact that the personal data we hold about you is accurate: in this case, the processing operations in relation to this data will be put on hold for the period during which this is verified.

    * You have objected to a processing activity based on (a) legitimate interest(s): in this case, you can require the processing operation to be put on hold while we verify the grounds for processing.

    * You consider that the processing is unlawful but you object to erasure and request restriction, instead.

    * We have no further need for the data but you require it to establish, exercise, or defend legal claims.

Despite your request, we may continue the processing of your personal data if we have to establish, exercise, or defend legal claims. We will notify you before lifting a restriction.

  6. Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority

If you consider that our processing of your personal data infringes the GDPR or any other applicable national laws, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, (in particular in the Member State where you live, place of work or of an alleged infringement of the GDPR).

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may occasionally amend this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our services and the way we handle your personal information or changes in the applicable laws.

If we make changes we consider important, we will let you know by placing a notice on the relevant site and/or contact you using other methods such as email.

To the extent permitted by applicable law, such changes will be applicable from the time they are published on our site, unless we specify a date of entry into force. Your continued use of our site from that day on will be subject to the new Privacy Policy.

## How to Contact Us?

If you have any comments or questions about this privacy policy or generally about our privacy practices, please send an email to [privacy@livejasmin.com](mailto:privacy@livejasmin.com) or via mail to the address indicated below, and we will get back to you quickly. We are always glad to talk about our privacy practices.

Duodecad IT Services Luxembourg S.à r.l.  
44, Avenue John F. Kennedy  
L-1855, Luxembourg  
Grand Duchy of Luxembourg  

We are also happy to inform you that we have an employee dedicated to ensuring your privacy, our Data Protection Officer. You can directly reach our Data Protection Officer via email at: [dpo@livejasmin.com](mailto:dpo@livejasmin.com) or mail to the following address:

To the attention of the DPO  
Duodecad IT Services Luxembourg S.à r.l.  
44, Avenue John F. Kennedy  
L-1855, Luxembourg  
Grand Duchy of Luxembourg
